Outbreath UP137
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Outbreath
1998 -- 2011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP137
0.5 Linear Feet
12 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the biannual issues of Outbreath, an undergraduate student publication containing short fiction and artwork. It was published once per semester between 1998 and 2011. It was succeeded by The Tufts Canon.
Biographical / Historical
Outbreath was a student literary group that published a journal by the same name on a semester schedule between 1998 and 2011.The focus of the publication was short stories and photography. They reported to the Media Advocacy Board. The group disbanded in 2011 and replaced by The Tufts Canon.
- Outbreath, 1998 -- 2011; UP137.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 12 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Outbreath, an undergraduate student publication containing short fiction and artwork published once per semester between 1998 and 2011.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Outbreath, Fall, 1998; UP137.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Issue
    1
  - Outbreath, Spring, 1999; UP137.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    2
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2000; UP137.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    4
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2000; UP137.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    5
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2001; UP137.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    6
  - Outbreath, 2002-04; UP137.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    8
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2002; UP137.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    9
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2003; UP137.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    10
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2003; UP137.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    11
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2004; UP137.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    12
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2005; UP137.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    13
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2005; UP137.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    14
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2006; UP137.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    15
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2006; UP137.001.001.00014
    16
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2007; UP137.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    17
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2007; UP137.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    18
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2008; UP137.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    19
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2008; UP137.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    20
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2009; UP137.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    21
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2009; UP137.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    22
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2010; UP137.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    23
  - Outbreath, Fall, 2010; UP137.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
    24
  - Outbreath, Spring, 2011; UP137.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    25